A Guide to the Theodore Malinin collection of Alexis Carrel and Charles Lindbergh papers FA208
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Experiment Files, 1906-1940; 3; 1.8 Cubic Feet
  - Experiment Files: Action of Protein Precipitate on the Growth of Embryonic Chick Heart Tissue (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Experiment Files: Action of Rat Serum on Normal Rat Fibroblasts (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Experiment Files: Action of Thyroid Extract upon Growth of Granulation Tissue (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Experiment Files: Action of Treated & Untreated Serum on the Rate of Growth of Homologous Fibroblasts (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Experiment Files: Action of Unheated and Heated Rabbit Serum on the Rate of Growth of Chicken Fibroblasts. Heated one hour at 65° C. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Experiment Files: Action of Unheated and Heated Sera from Young and Old Chickens on the Rate of Growth of Chicken Fibroblasts. Heated one hour at 65° C. (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Experiment Files: Action of Vitamine No. 75 & 145 from Dr. Levine (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Experiment Files: Arsenic Tumors (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Experiment Files: Bagg Strain - Mouse Carcinoma (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Experiment Files: Blood Charts - Rockefeller Mice - 2, 3, 4 mos (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Experiment Files: Blood Charts - Rockefeller Mice - 6, 7, 8 mos (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Experiment Files: Blood Charts - Rockefeller Mice - 1 yr (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Experiment Files: Blood Charts - Swiss Mice - 2, 3, 4 mos (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Experiment Files: Blood Charts - Swiss Mice - 6, 7, 8 mos (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Experiment Files: Blood Charts - Swiss Mice - 1 yr (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Experiment Files: Blood Charts - Swiss Mice - 2 yrs (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Experiment Files: Bone Marrow - Digest (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Experiment Files: Cancer - Bibliography on the Mortality of Cancer Acc. To Soc. Conditions (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Experiment Files: Cancer - Cultures of Adeno - Carcinoma (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Experiment Files: Cancer - Culture of Tumors (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Experiment Files: Cancer - Tumors (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Experiment Files: Carcinoma (Ehrlich") Experiments (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Experiment Files: Carrel - Artificial Regeneration of Nerves (plan of experiments), 1908 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Experiment Files: Carrel - Cultural Differences in Monocytes, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Experiment Files: Carrel and Dr. Foot - Experiments, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Experiment Files: Carrel - Individuality of Monocytes, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Experiment Files: Carrel's Experiments - Rous Sarcoma, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Experiment Files: Chemical Tumors - Action of Lipoid on Embryonic Pulp and On Chickens (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Experiment Files: Chemical Tumors - Arsenic Cultures (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Experiment Files: Chemical Tumors - Arsenic Tumor (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Experiment Files: Chemical Tumors - Coal Tar Tumors (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Experiment Files: Chemical Tumors - Indol Tumor (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Experiment Files: Chemical Tumors - Toxic Action of Arsenic (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Experiment Files: Chicken 5979 - Effect of Time on Serum Stored in Ice Box (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Experiment Files: Cicatrization of Wounds - Pig (Completed Charts), 1928-1929 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Experiment Files: Coal Tar on Chicken Tissues, folder 1 of 2 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Experiment Files: Coal Tar on Chicken Tissues, folder 2 of 2 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Experiment Files: Completed Guinea Pig Experiments, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Experiment Files: Cultivation of Pig Skin in Chick Plasma. Guinea in Chick Plasma (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Experiment Files: Digest of Ether Extracted Pituitary - Naterior Lobe - X- 484, X- 485, X- 556, and Control (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Experiment Files: Dilution of Serum (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Experiment Files: Dr. Baker's Report of Her Experiments to Dr. Carrel, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Experiment Files: Dr. Ebeling - Action of Chick Embryo Juice; Normal Rat Fibroblasts (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Experiment Files: Dr. Ebeling - Drawings - Bone Marrow and Sarcoma (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Experiment Files: Dr. Ebeling - Effect of Alcoholic Solution of Calf Liver Digest on Rat Sarcoma (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Experiment Files: Dr. Ebeling - Effect of Calf Liver Digest on Normal and Sarcomatous Rat Fibroblasts (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Experiment Files: Dr. Ebeling - Effect of Calf Liver Digest on Sarcomatous Rat Fibroblasts (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Experiment Files: Dr. Ebeling - Effect of Chicken Plasma on Normal and Sarcomatous Fibroblasts (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Experiment Files: Dr. Ebeling - Effect of Dr. Heidelberger's Calf Liver Digest on Sarcomatous Rat Fibroblasts (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Experiment Files: Dr. Ebeling - Effect of Glucose on Fibroblasts, Leukocytes, and Epithelial Cells (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Experiment Files: Dr. Ebeling - Effect of Keratin on Sarcomatous Rat Fibroblasts (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Experiment Files: Dr. Ebeling - Effect of Kidney Digest 1: 8 on Sarcomatous Rat Fibroblasts (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Experiment Files: Dr. Ebeling - Effect of Pituitary Digest on Normal Rat Fibroblasts (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Experiment Files: Dr. Ebeling - Effect of Rat Serum on Sarcomatous Rat Fibroblasts (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Experiment Files: Dr. Ebeling - Old Exp. Effect of Heated and Unheated Rabbit Serum, Mixture No. 7 (Dr. Baker), Fibrin Digest, Sodium Glycerophosphate (in clot and fluid media), 1/8/37 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Experiment Files: Dr. Ebeling - Original - Table and Charts for Sarcoma #10 Article (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Experiment Files: Dr. Ebeling - Residual Activity of Normal Rat Fibroblasts (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Experiment Files: Dr. Ebeling - Sarcomatous Fibroblasts (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Experiment Files: Dr. Flexner - Mousery, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Experiment Files: The Effect of the Variation in the Osmotic Tension and of the Dilution of Culture Media on the Cell Proliferation of Connective Tissue, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Experiment Files: Ebeling - Epithelium - Method of Tissue Culture and the Cultivation of Whole Organs (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Experiment Files: Ebeling - Morphological Appearance of Pathological Cells (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Experiment Files: Effect of Absence of Ca and Excess Potassium on Tissues (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Experiment Files: Effect of Chicken Bone Marrow and Testicle Extracts on Chick Spleen (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Experiment Files: Effect of Chicken Serum on Sarcomatous Rat Fibroblasts (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Experiment Files: Effect of Heparin on Old Strain, Spleen, and Muscle Fibroblasts (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Experiment Files: Effect of Hypotonic Medium on Tissues (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Experiment Files: Effect of Nutritive Substances with Cat Serum on Mouse Tumors - Strain I (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Experiment Files: Effect of Nutritive Substances with Rat Serum on Mouse Tumors - Strain I (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Experiment Files: Effect of Nutritive Substances without Serum on Mouse Tumors - Strain I (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Experiment Files: Effect of Nutritive Substances without Serum on Mouse Tumors - Strain II (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Experiment Files: Effect of pH on Rabbit Bone Marrow and Leukocytes (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Experiment Files: Effect of Tyrode Solution and Chick Embryo Juice on Normal and Sarcomatous Rat Fibroblasts (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Experiment Files: Experiments on Rabbit Tissues - Different Media and Pneumococcus, 1929-1930 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Experiment Files: Extract from Human Thyroid (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Experiment Files: Fibrin and Serum as a Culture Medium (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Experiment Files: Fischer Strain Mouse Carcinoma (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Experiment Files: General Statement on the Control of Osmotic Tension of Artificial Media Used in the Carrel - Lindbergh Pump, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Experiment Files: Growth Hormone on Epithelium (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Experiment Files: Heated Serum (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Experiment Files: Hemorrhages (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Experiment Files: Human Fibroblasts - Notes, etc. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Experiment Files: Human Leukocytes - Normal and Pathological - Dr. Rhoad's (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Experiment Files: Influence of Heated and Unheated Sera on the Growth of Fibroblasts - New Series (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Experiment Files: Influence of Iodized Blood Clot on the Gr. In Vivo of Connective Tissue of Cats, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Experiment Files: Jensen Sarcoma (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Experiment Files: Jensen Sarcoma - Cinema Tracings (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Experiment Files: Jensen Rat Sarcoma (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Experiment Files: Jensen Sarcoma - Effect of Rat Bone Marrow on Jensen Sarcoma (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Experiment Files: Jensen Sarcoma - Effect of Spleen on Jensen Sarcoma Fibroblasts (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Experiment Files: Jensen Sarcoma - In Calf Liver Digest (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Experiment Files: Jensen Sarcoma - In Rat and Chicken Serum (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Experiment Files: Jensen Sarcoma in Serum and La Tapie (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Experiment Files: Jensen Sarcoma - Residual Energy (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Experiment Files: Lathrop Strain - Black Charts (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Experiment Files: Lathrop Strain Mouse Carcinoma (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Experiment Files: Liver Digest on Human Tissue (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Experiment Files: Liver Digest on Sarcomatous Rat Fibroblasts (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Experiment Files: The Mechanism of the Formation of Sarcoma (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Experiment Files: Memorandum as to a Proposed Center of Integrated Scientific Research, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Experiment Files: Methods Used by Dr. Carrel in Tissue Culture Experiments (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Experiment Files: Miscellaneous. Exp.- Tumor Transplant, Strains, Pulling Strength, and Constitution Index (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Experiment Files: Mouse Blood Study - RIMR (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Experiment Files: Mousery - Autopsy Diagnoses, folder 1 of 2 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Experiment Files: Mousery - Autopsy Diagnoses, folder 2 of 2 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Experiment Files: Mousery (Dr. Macnab) Pt. II - Seventy Nutrition Exper, 1933 June (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Experiment Files: Mousery - Manuscript, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Experiment Files: Mousery - Manuscripts (includes Tables and Charts), 1933 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Experiment Files: Mousery - Monograph (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Experiment Files: Mousery - Rockefeller Charts (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Experiment Files: Mousery - Tumors (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Experiment Files: Mousery - Weights (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Experiment Files: Mousery - Weight Curves (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Experiment Files: Normal Mouse Tissue in Digests of Fibrin - No Serum (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Experiment Files: Normal Rat Fibroblasts (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Experiment Files: Old Records - Tumor Graphs; Weights (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Experiment Files: Ovarian Chicken Tumors (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Experiment Files: Pig Drawings, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Experiment Files: Pituitary Digest on Sarcomatous Fibroblasts (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Experiment Files: Rabbit Connective Tissue Extracts (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Experiment Files: Rabbit Tissue Extracts on Rabbit Bone Marrow and Rabbit Lymph Gland (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Experiment Files: Rat Sarcoma Drawings, 1926-1927 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Experiment Files: Rat Sarcoma # 39, 1928-1929 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Experiment Files: Rate of Growth of Fibroblasts in Serum kept for 232 Days in Cold Storage and in Serum Freshly Obtained from the Same Animal (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Experiment Files: Rate of Skin Regeneration (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Experiment Files: Residual Energy of Mouse Tumors (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Experiment Files: Rous Virus, 1930-1931 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Experiment Files: Serum Variable - Action on Growth within Presence of Tissue Juice. Constant Volume (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Experiment Files: Spontaneous Mouse Tumors, 1930-1931 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Experiment Files: Swiss Charts - Exp. 25-107 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Experiment Files: Swiss Mouse Carcinoma (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Experiment Files: Tissue Culture (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Experiment Files: Tissue Culture Notes - Exp. No. 14099 to 15364, 1919 July 23-1920 January 3 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Experiment Files: Weights of Organs of One Year Old Mice from Six Strains (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Experiment Notebooks, 1925-1939; 4; 1 Cubic Feet
  Hardbound volumes containing notes and charts. Related to animal experiments and tissue culture experiments completed between 1925 and 1935. Also includes Volumes 7-13 of the notebooks referring to Carrel's experimental work with Charles Lindbergh.
  - Experiment Notebooks: Book B - Vol. 4 - Animal Experiments - Exp. 644B, Exp. 988B, 1925 April 17-June 5 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Experiment Notebooks: Book D - Vol. 58 - Exp. 14753D, Exp. 14857, 1933 February 24-April 18 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Experiment Notebooks: Book D - Vol. 71 - Exp. 16163D, Exp. 16287D, 1935 March 25-May 4 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Experiment Notebooks: Lindbergh Exps. Vol. 7 - #426L, #501L, 1937 February 23-April 14 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Experiment Notebooks: Lindbergh Exps. Vol. 8 - #502L, #575L, 1937 April 14-November 5 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Experiment Notebooks: Lindbergh Exps. Vol. 9 - #576L, # 648L, 1937 November 8-December 16 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Experiment Notebooks: Lindbergh Exps. Vol. 10 - #649L, #725L, 1937 December 16-1938 January 28 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Experiment Notebooks: Lindbergh Exps. Vol. 11 - #726L, #800L, 1938 January 28-March 10 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Experiment Notebooks: Lindbergh Exps. Vol. 12 - #801L, #865L, 1938 March 11-May 31 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Experiment Notebooks: Lindbergh Exps. Vol. 13 - #866L, #989L, 1938 May 21-1939 May 11 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Malinin Files, 1910-1977; 5; 1 Cubic Feet
  Contains copies of Carrel correspondence, excerpts of letters from Carrel, obituaries, memoir materials on Carrel and Lindbergh, publications, listings of materials in the Carrel Collection at Georgetown University, reprints, unpublished manuscripts of Carrel, a bibliography of Carrel's works, notes and book outlines compiled by Malinin for his book on Carrel.
  - Malinin Files: [Alexis Carrel Collection] (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Malinin Files: Alexis Carrel Papers (Georgetown) - T. Malinin & C. Lindbergh (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Malinin Files: A Study of Documents and Personal Papers - Theodore Malinin (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Malinin Files: [Books Contained in the Carrel Collection] (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Malinin Files: Carrel Centennial/ G.U. Letter to J. Rose (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Malinin Files: Carrel Letters - part I, 1935-1945 1935-1939; bulk (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Malinin Files: Carrel Letters - part II, 1935-1945 1940-1941; bulk (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Malinin Files: Carrel Letters, 1937-1941 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Malinin Files: Carrel Letters, 1942-1944 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Malinin Files: Carrel, the man (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Malinin Files: Mrs. Carrel (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Malinin Files: [Carrel Papers - Correspondence] (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Malinin Files: [Carrel References] (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Malinin Files: Carrel's Scientific Staff (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Malinin Files: Carrel's Unpublished MSS (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Malinin Files: [Carrel Xeroxes] (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Malinin Files: Cornelius Clifford, Rev (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Malinin Files: [Copies] (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Malinin Files: Miss Crutcher 9PEX-270-A) (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Malinin Files: Ebeling - Reprints (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Malinin Files: French Foundation for the Study of Human Problems, folder 1 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Malinin Files: French Foundation for the Study of Human Problems, folder 2 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Malinin Files: French Foundation for the Study of Human Problems, folder 3 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Malinin Files: The Georgetown University Alexis Carrel Collection, folder 1 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Malinin Files: The Georgetown University Alexis Carrel Collection, folder 2 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Malinin Files: Historical Developments in Preservation (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Malinin Files: [Letter Excerpts], folder 1 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Malinin Files: [Letter Excerpts], folder 2 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Malinin Files: Letters to Guigou, folder 1 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Malinin Files: Letters to Guigou, folder 2 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Malinin Files: Letters to Guigou, folder 3 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Malinin Files: Mr. Charles A. Lindbergh (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Malinin Files: Lindbergh Obituary (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Malinin Files: Lourdes (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Malinin Files: [Malinin - Copies] (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Malinin Files: [Malinin - Correspondence] *, folder 1 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Malinin Files: [Malinin - Correspondence], folder 2 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Malinin Files: [Malinin - Correspondence], folder 3 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Malinin Files: [Malinin - Notes], folder 1 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Malinin Files: [Malinin - Notes], folder 2 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Malinin Files: [Malinin - Notes], folder 3 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Malinin Files: Man, the Unknown (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Malinin Files: Master Copy of Reprints by DuNouy (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Malinin Files: Eugene Mayer (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Malinin Files: Mousery Report, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Malinin Files: Myeloblasts (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Malinin Files: James D. Newton (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Malinin Files: New York (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Malinin Files, 1914-1923 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Malinin Files: Organ Culture (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Malinin Files: Parker *operating mask contained within (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Malinin Files: Dr. Raymond Parker (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Malinin Files: Private Letters & Notes Translated from French (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Malinin Files: [Papers with A. Carrel as Subject] (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Malinin Files: ["Recollections of an Eyewitness"- Charles A. Lindbergh - by Richard J. Bing] (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Malinin Files: Religion (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Malinin Files: [Reprints Published in French,], 1923 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Malinin Files: Mr. Charles T. Riall (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Malinin Files: RIMR, folder 1 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Malinin Files: RIMR, folder 2 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Malinin Files: Scientific Method (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Malinin Files: T.M. Jeger (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Malinin Files: Transplantation - Matas (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Malinin Files: Transplantation of Organs (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Malinin Files: Transplantation of Organs - P.A. Levene; Dr. Meltzer (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Malinin Files: Dr. L.G. Walker, Jr. (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Malinin Files: [War Demonstration Hospital] (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Malinin Files: WWII, folder 1 of 4 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Malinin Files: WWII, folder 2 of 4 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Malinin Files: WWII, folder 3 of 4 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Malinin Files: WWII, folder 4 of 4 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Malinin Files: Yves Christian Book (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Malinin Files: Miscellaneous, folder 1 of 5 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Malinin Files: Miscellaneous, folder 2 of 5 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Malinin Files: Miscellaneous, folder 3 of 5 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Malinin Files: Miscellaneous, folder 4 of 5 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Malinin Files: Miscellaneous, folder 5 of 5 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Malinin Book Files: [Chapter Notes], folder 1 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Malinin Book Files: [Chapter Notes], folder 2 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Malinin Book Files: [Chapter Notes/ Book Outline] (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Malinin Book Files: [Chapter & Interview Notes (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Malinin Book Files: Corrected Rough I (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Malinin Book Files: Corrected Rough IV (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Malinin Book Files: Corrected Rough VI (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Slides-Carrel/Malinin, 1914-1977; 6; 0.8 Cubic Feet
  Contains both black and white and color projection slides. The Carrel slides are replicas of glass negatives related to Carrel's work during WWI in France and the development of the Carrel-Dakin Solution. They also contain slides related to vascular suturing as well as personal slides of Carrel, his wife and their home in France. The Malinin slides relate to presentation material regarding Carrel and his work with Charles Lindbergh on a perfusion pump.
  Arranged in alphabetical order by individual.
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 18, Folder 3)